This is the last game.
He's called in a arranging and the home.
This is a film called in the release
of the might of two-year-old home.
This is a film called the
Guilherme Professor of Columbia,
Theū, the Emperor, the pirate,
themost and the last ones we live in.
The original play of
the Harry Potter, Dude,
this is the theme called
in the scheduledключens.
The original movie, I'm a kid?
Look, the king on the list,
I'm a kid who's a kid
who's a kid who is a kid.
Get over here, the morons!
Miss Nagi, this is the
maid who offed Ronko.
One of my maids caught her sliming around.
Which cafe is she from?
Wuv Wuv Moonbeam,
the one that Ronco wiped out right
after getting out of the slammer.
Do you have any idea what you've done?
You don't own me!
I'm not your creature, nor
am I an axolotl either!
I'm a friggin' black space bunny!
Wuv Wuv Moonbeam is the
only homo I'll ever know!
Were you seeking revenge?
Hey boss, should she
sleep with the fishes?
What do you say?
An enjoyable maid cafe, how funny.
You can release her now.
Uh, but boss - Don't make me say it twice.
Yes, ma 'am.
Squeak all you want, it'll do you no good.
You're a creature now.
Let's see you prove your worth. Huh?
What is that supposed to mean?
The time has come to go
full bore on those swine.
Prepare for an all-out war.
Damn maids I really wish
they wouldn't use the
same funeral hall it's
another gang war casualty.
Isn't it I heard this
maid got out of prison
less than a year ago I
bet she deserved it I just
Wish Akiba could be rid
of all these maid cafes
Where are the police when
you need them not so Loud
you never know what they'll
do if they hear us Did
you hear the news that
Ronko Manon's dead That's
what the porker gets for
getting cocky a 36 year
old maid dying feels like
the end of a Bygone era,
you know what I mean?
Damn straight, bear friend.
The other swine will be quick to follow,
so she won't be alone for very long.
It just goes to show you that Akiba needs
more beef than pork, you know what I mean?
Okay, see ya. See you later.
Tell me where I can find
the maid who killed Ronko.
You're that pig from Oinky Doink.
Who killed Ronko?
How the hell should I fucking know?
Now we can tag your ear like
the useless heifer you are.
How about I give you a nose ring next?
All right, all right, just stop!
I'll talk, I'll talk, okay?
The worthless scum that killed Ronko.
It's a maid that used to
work at Wov Wov Moonbeam.
Did the head give the order?
I don't know anything about that,
but I do know the head's rounding up soldiers
and weapons to crush the oinky-doink.
And where is she right now?
You think an anderling maid
like me would know that answer?
Come on, let them go!
Now you go tell the other creatures.
Nagomi Wajira is in mourning.
Tell them I'm black pork now.
I want to know about the
maid named Uzuko who used
to work upstairs when it
was the maid tea room.
Never heard of her.
I don't have time for this.
I need you to tell me where she lives now.
Why the heck would I know that?
Then where do her parents live?
Like I said, I don't know anything.
Is that Ronko's gun?
If you have some time, I'll
tell you a bit about the past.
It was 20-something years ago.
A maid named Michio brought an
orphan named Uzuko home with her.
Even as a kid, her eyes always
looked starved for something.
That was back when Michio
had a steel grip and
was well known as a
warmonger maid in Akiba.
She intended to raise
Uzuko as her successor.
But it wasn't until Ronko joined
the cafe that Michio changed.
I think Ronko's innocent
sincerity rubbed off on her.
Michio changed her policy to make the Maid
Tea House a cafe that
didn't rely on violence.
A far cry from what it was.
But Uzuko,
as starved as she was, couldn't bear
to see Michio give up all the violence.
Jisoo!
And so Usoko arranged a hit
on Michio and killed her.
And now, sadly, Ronko's dead as well.
Usoko has no place she can call home now,
so I reckon she doesn't
even have an address.
Not that I would know that.
She craves immense power because
she's afraid of being all alone.
But that power is why she is all alone.
She's a sad, foolish creature.
If you don't intend to eat anything,
I'm going to need you to get out.
Sorry for the trouble.
Hey, you're not going to eat?
Nagomi, where have you been all this time?
You're still wearing that thing?
You didn't even come to the funeral.
Hey! What? Nagomi?
Where's the key?
It's a chip, is it?
Excuse me, what do you think you're doing?
The creatures are coming for us.
For real?
We're going to need a lot of guns.
So you're just going to steal
the cafe's money to buy weapons?
We don't have any time to spare.
If we don't get prepared
quick, they'll slaughter us.
You need to calm down.
How can you be calm right now?
You're all still maids, aren't you?
They just took out one of our own.
If they kill one of ours,
we take out one of theirs.
Isn't that what maids do?
Zoya, get ready.
Look, I'm gonna send as many
goddamn creatures to hell as I can.
Then I'm gonna see Ronko
there with a smile on my face.
Nerula, please forgive
me for having to change.
Sorry I disappointed you.
Well, well, well.
You sure got me the
utter day, ugly pig face.
You think you pigs can get off?
What's going on over there?
Here, have an otter one!
And an otter!
So, are you satisfied?
Is that enough to satisfy you?
Time to die, pig.
Is this about...
Is this all what being a
maid's about? What's that?
All this threatening and beating and
killing, is that really all the fun for you?
Do you find enjoyment in
making people scared of you?
What the hell's wrong with her?
What's the point of being a maid, huh?
Come tell me!
I think she must have snapped
from getting clobbered too much.
I'll enter right here.
Hey, there's too many
people around right now.
You better not.
Fine.
She's only got a few
days left to live anyway.
Hey, aren't you mates?
Hey, let's have some more fun!
We can be mates together!
She should have just thrown
this shabby thing away.
Who keeps this kind of silly thing anyway?
Is this dirt?
Jeez, why would you want that?
Just look at how awful I look.
Damn it, she wants us
to raid the pigsty now?
We don't have the time to prepare.
Are you seriously questioning
the head's decision?
That's not what I mean.
But still, I have no idea what
the head is thinking nowadays.
It's ever since that Ronco
maid got out of the joint.
She disowned the pigsty,
then took them back, and now she's trying
to crush those damn hogs once again.
It's not easy to cope with. True that.
Maybe it's time for Miss
Noggy's reign to come to an end.
Nagomi!
Where the hell did you run off to?
What the hell?
What happened to your face?
Nagomi, we're ready to stand up and fight.
Time to avenge Ranko.
We'll take down as many of them as we can.
If it's a war they want, let's
grit our teeth and just go for it.
Nagomi?
At first, I wasn't so sure
about Ranko as a maid.
She didn't have a heart,
she looked dead serious,
and she killed people on her first day.
But now, I understand that being
a maid with Ronko was so much fun.
She said that Oinky Doink was her family.
I don't want to lose this place either.
This is my home too.
But the creatures are
coming for us, aren't they?
It'll be a fight to the death.
We're creatures too, after all.
Do you enjoy the way Oinky
Doink is now, Shipon?
Are your masters feeling the
love when they come home?
Is your mouth turned upwards?
My mouth is very sad.
But there's nothing we
can do about it now.
I think we can do anything we want.
Because we are maids.
You have something in mind then?
We'll spring a maid war on those bitches.
Moose Nagi, would you consider
exterminating the pigs at a later date?
We haven't paid off the cops yet.
If we cause much more bloodshed, a fair
number of maids will end up in the slammer.
We stick to the plan.
You mentioned that you want
to take part in the slaughter.
Are you serious? I am.
Whittle Teddy here thinks you shouldn't.
If anything were to
happen, I couldn't bear it.
Any maids who refuse to obey me will die.
Large ramen, extra veggies, topped
with sauce and a load of garlic.
Six of them, please, sir.
Make that seven, old man.
Sure.
Nogomi, let me have some
of that ramen, please.
I want some of that ramen, too.
Looks delicious.
Can I have a slurp, please?
It's been a while since
you've been here, Uzuko.
Ronko's dead.
She...
I'm about to slaughter the hogs.
Better get lost. Did you know?
Ronko still called you her sister.
Enough.
I just wish you and Ronko could
have had my ramen one life.
Dipping noodles are the
new thing now, old man.
Damn dipping noodles.
Let's go.
Welcome home to the pigsty!
Pigsty?
Wow, I can't believe we have
so many mistresses here.
What a sweet, sweet surprise!
Are you, like, super nervous
because we're crazy cute?
Come on, mistresses, relax!
There are lots of cute maids
here at Oinky Doink Cafe.
Cute maids?
We've come to slaughter you.
That's great, Oinky Doink.
But first, why not experience some
of our love here at Oinky Doink Cafe?
You shitting me?
Welcome, mistresses.
Today happens to be our big
bang lovey-dovey heart event.
Any cute mistress with a gun will get
to enjoy all of our services for free.
Shall I kill them?
There's 26 of us.
Porky very much.
You heard her. Take a seat.
This here is our charming
brick house where us
cute little pigs live
called the Oinky Doink Cafe.
We are here to become the finest
Iberico pork to feed our humans.
Us piglets have been waiting
to serve all of you mistresses.
Oink!
I'm hungry, jackass! Jackass?
There are no rabbits
or donkeys here, silly.
It's just a house of piglets.
Miss Nagi, I heard you were once
a maid here in this very location.
That was long ago.
Pretty mistresses, allow me to
please take your oinkters right away.
What would you suggest?
I recommend the live
pork-formance oinky-doink special.
We'll get that for all of us.
But once the pork-formance
is over, you all die.
You have a very wise snout, mistress.
Watch as they make this drink here extra
tasty with the health of a snort snort.
When I say oinky smooch,
you say snorty snort, okay?
Ready and oinky smooch.
Snort!
Getting embarrassed at a maid
cafe like this is not oink-ay.
Especially you mistress.
Get that scowl off your
face. That's it! Time to die!
Relax.
I'll kill her myself later.
Thank you, oinky-doink!
The hell?
It's like you've given up being human.
Okay, here we go!
Oinky smooch?
Snorty snorty. Doinky smooch?
Snorty snorty. Oinky-doink!
Doink! Doink! Oh, yay!
Thanks to you all, your drinks
are now so much tastier!
Why does this will taste so good damn
it why'd you turn off the damn light
We're not gonna take this crap
huh welcome ham so much for coming
I'm so happy to see so
many of you here allowing
us to entertain you
today we're here to kill
you You bitch-ass porker
thank you oinky doink
i'm nagomi and i'm here
to sing just for you
Spark with you to the prime Come
to me i'm sublime Super duper
showtime Understand Take a seat
and listen To my cinderella story
What is that?
I'm gonna tell you.
If ever your soul is feeling worn out?
I have a lovely gift for you.
This beautiful smile.
And even these tears.
Have sparkling love infused in them all.
Here you go.
She needs sharper moves.
Wait, hold on.
You need sharper moves.
Watch me, that part should
go something like this.
Oh, I get it now.
You're so very good at this.
I'm so lucky to have you.
I hope I'll be a wonderful
maid like you someday.
Silly, picky, tricky.
That's how a girl's heart works.
Maybe that's selfish.
I'm so sorry.
Time for my own future.
Come on, everyone!
So many dreams to me come true.
I'm gonna strive hard to pursue.
So right now, you never
know who I will be?
Till the day comes and
I'm who I want to be!
Even when it's like your
life's still tolerable.
Tolerable, got it, got it,
on it, I'm so real powerful!
Powerful, are you ready to go?
See me as I sparkle, my
world shining bright.
So exciting, what a thrill!
Everyday busy, oh my god!
So much sparkle, heart aglow.
In time, I feel 17.
So exciting, what a thrill!
So I feel the trouble, all in fun.
So much sparkle, heart aglow.
Adore it all with a pretty heart.
Love means do
Yeah!
Why, Ms. Noggy?
Their applause means nothing.
So many things have happened since I've
arrived here in Akiba
I've seen maids who were
terrifying die and I've
seen maids who were dear
to me die as well everyone
on all sides killed
so many to avenge the
maids who died but I I
don't find that to be
any fun at all why should
cute maids have to hit each other how does
using guns help spread
more love if you don't
pull the trigger then
you get killed a maid
either takes or gets
taken from you need to be
strong in order to
survive here a maid's job
is to serve others like
a maid I respect once
said Oinky Doink Cafe
is cat pig to serve as
a home to all masters
hello and welcome home
my mistress so this is
my home now that's right
starting today this is
your home welcome home
cut the sentimental crap in the
end a maid ultimately ends up
alone mistress if you ever feel
lonely please try coming home.
to Oinky Doink Cafe again.
I promise you we'll make
you feel the moi moi kyun.
Your name's Nagomi, right? Yes.
You're a shitty maid who doesn't even
come close to being like Miss Michio.
Instead, you're a maid
who's exactly like Ronko.
Oh, well, that's such an honor.
So, mistress, were you able
to enjoy Oinky Doink Cafe?
That's what I'm trying to do
I'm going to look at you I'm
going to look at you I can't
wait for you How can I still
feel every single one's dreams?
While I can tell them to be a
one's
life,
Take care,
take care, take care.
You are who you are,
Tell me to tell you.
You probably don't know,
but Akiba used to be a really rough
neighborhood, with gunfights and all that.
Gunfights in Akiba?
Are you serious?
Doesn't seem possible, does it? Uh, no.
So, why this cafe in particular?
So as to see our favorite maid, of course.
A favorite, huh?
What kind of maid is she?
A 36-year-old maid. What? She's 36?
Here she comes.
Hello and welcome home, cute master.